Guide to the Asian CineVision Records TAM.416
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Video Recordings
  - Video 051: CCTV Apr 24, 1977 Broadcast tape Special Report: Kung Fu Match II, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1681 (Box 80)
    Duration: 30:17
  - Video 052: CCTV May 1, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Nov 21-May 1, 1978; cuid1682 (Box 80)
    Duration: 34:17
  - Video 053: CCTV May 1, 1977 Broadcast tape Profile: Hsia Yang, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1683 (Box 81)
  - Video 054: CCTV May 8, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1684 (Box 81)
    Duration: 29:17
  - Video 055: CCTV May 8, 1977 Broadcast tape Special Report: A Talk with Two Mothers, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1685 (Box 81)
    Duration: 31:05
  - Video 056: CCTV May 15, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1686 (Box 81)
    Duration: 35:00
  - Video 057: CCTV May 15, 1977 Broadcast tape Drama "The World of Ah Sing", May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1687 (Box 81)
  - Video 058: CCTV May 22, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1688 (Box 81)
    Duration: 30:44
  - Video 059: CCTV May 29, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1689 (Box 81)
    Duration: 33:26
  - Video 060: CCTV Jun 5, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1690 (Box 81)
    Duration: 31:42
  - Video 061: CCTV Jun 12, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1691 (Box 81)
  - Video 062: CCTV Jun 12, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1692 (Box 81)
    Duration: 25:27
  - Video 063: CCTV Jun 19, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1693 (Box 81)
    Duration: 33:09
  - Video 064: CCTV Jun 26, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1694 (Box 81)
    Duration: 33:11
  - Video 065: CCTV Jul 3, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1695 (Box 81)
  - Video 066: CCTV Jul 3, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1696 (Box 81)
    Duration: 29:38
  - Video 067: CCTV Jul 10, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1697 (Box 81)
    Duration: 32:40
  - Video 068: CCTV Jul 10, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1698 (Box 81)
    Duration: 28:09
  - Video 069: CCTV Jul 17, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1699 (Box 81)
    Duration: 32:09
  - Video 070: CCTV Jul 17, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1700 (Box 81)
    Duration: 33:28
  - Video 071: CCTV Jul 24, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1701 (Box 81)
  - Video 072: CCTV Jul 31, 1977 Broadcast tape, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1702 (Box 81)
  - Video 073: CCTV Aug 7, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Village Voice in Chinatown, Teng and Wah and China, Construction site demonstration, CIA on mind control, New York black out, Bombing, Occupations, Nixon's interview, San Francisco hotel strike, cultural, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1703 (Box 81)
    Duration: 28:13
  - Video 074: CCTV Aug 14, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1704 (Box 81)
    Duration: 31:16
  - Video 075: CCTV Aug 21, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1705 (Box 81)
    Duration: 30:32
  - Video 076: CCTV Aug 21, 1977 Broadcast tape Special Report: CCTV Production and Performance, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1706 (Box 81)
  - Video 077: CCTV Aug 28, 1977 Broadcast tape News, May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1707 (Box 81)
    Duration: 30:15
  - Video 078: CCTV Aug 28, 1977 Broadcast tape Drama "War and Peace", May 1-Aug 28, 1978; cuid1708 (Box 81)
    Duration: 31:46
  - Video 079: Sep 4, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1709 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 079)
    Duration: 30:34
  - Video 080: Sep 4, 1977 Broadcast tape, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1710 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 080)
    Duration: 30:45
  - Video 081: Sep 9, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Mayoral candidate campaign at Silver Palace, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1711 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 081)
    Duration: 31:45
  - Video 082: Sep 11, 1977 Broadcast tape Year End Special, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1712 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 082)
    Duration: 32:47
  - Video 083: Sep 11, 1977 Broadcast tape First Anniversary, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1713 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 083)
    Duration: 32:24
  - Video 084: Oct 2, 1977 Broadcast tape Special Discussion: Mayoral candidate in Chinatown, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1714 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 084)
    Duration: 32:14
  - Video 085: Oct 9, 1977 Broadcast tape News, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1715 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 085)
    Duration: 32:55
  - Video 086: Oct 9, 1977 Broadcast tape Cultural Festival (CPC Festival II) (Repeat), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1716 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 086)
    Duration: 30:25
  - Video 087: Nov 1977 Broadcast tape, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1717 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 087)
    Duration: 30:02
  - Video 088: Nov 6, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Mayoral candidate campaign, Carter's increase of minimum wage, Health Clinic's fund raising dinner, Mobilization for Youth demonstrations against Union, Hong Kong police complaints against corruption, New York, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1718 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 088)
    Duration: 32:53
  - Video 089: Nov 13, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Ed Koch elected as mayor of New York City, Hong Kong police demonstration against corruption problems, photo exhibit at Center Street, Social Services focus on mental health, Taiwan donated a painting to St., Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1719 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 089)
    Duration: 32:54
  - Video 090: Nov 20, 1977 Broadcast tape News (, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1720 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 090)
    Duration: 25:07
  - Video 091: Nov 27, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Koch and campaign staff appointment, Asian American women conference, Middle East, Lisa Chow, Social Services interview with Mrs. Fong Min, Manpower training program), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1721 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 091)
    Duration: 28:45
  - Video 092: Dec 4, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Lincoln's Savings Bank Grand Opening, Bakke Case), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1722 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 092)
    Duration: 33:01
  - Video 093: Dec 11, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Sadat and Begin peace talks, Social Services with Dr. Yang Lung San on physical health, Liz Young and Ken Chin demonstration, Peking Opera at Merrill Bertrum), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1723 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 093)
    Duration: 31:11
  - Video 094: Dec 25, 1977 Broadcast tape News (Garment Workers Union 5 Chinese Board of Directors elected, CPC Adult Education Center graduation ceremony, Social Services interview with Mrs. Chan Duk Wah from the National Bank of North America), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1724 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 094)
    Duration: 28:37
  - Video 095: Jan 8, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Carter's trip to Iran, Poland, India, etc., return of the Crown to Hungry by the U.S., Carey's proposal for income tax reduction, Edward Koch's executive order for equal employment for gay/lesbians, Chinatown, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1725 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 095)
    Duration: 27:29
  - Video 096: Jan 15, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Edward Koch agrees to wage increase for city workers, Vietnam and Cambodia, Liz Young and Ken Chin Press Conference, Pang Jik Kun postponement of hearings, California proposes banning of smoking, Social Servi, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1726 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 096)
    Duration: 32:59
  - Video 097: Jan 22, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Carter's State of the Union address, debating the Middle East question, Pang case press conference with Morgenthau and interview with MB Lee, conflict between Vietnam and Cambodia, death of Herbert H. Humphrey, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1727 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 097)
    Duration: 32:35
  - Video 098: Jan 29, 2978 Broadcast tape News (Interview with Goji at the Democratic National Committee in Washington, DC, Ten Sau Pin visits Burma and Nepal, United Democratic Party Breakfast and interview with Carol Bellamy and Virginia Kee, Bella Abzug, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1728 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 098)
    Duration: 31:28
  - Video 099: Feb 5, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Ed Koch goes to Washington, Pan Am has low fare to the Orient and around the World trip, Old Age Center year-end dinner, Jimmy Carter on the Middle East, Asian American Film Festival interview with Tom Tam, In, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1729 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 099)
  - Video 100: Feb 5, 1978 Broadcast tape News (New Year Celebration by the Chinese students at Pace college including singing and karate by William Louie and dancing by the New York Chinese Dance Company, CPB meeting at the Summit Hotel with speakers Mrs., Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1730 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 100)
  - Video 101: Feb 12, 1978 Broadcast tape New Year welcome, CPC New Year dinner at Silver Palace with interviews with CPC's Charles Wang, Alan Cohen by Corky Lee, An introduction of the Cultural Festival program, Panama Canal Issue, Pace Hispanic Ballet by, Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1731 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 101)
  - Video 102: Feb 19, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Nixon's Board, Jimmy carter decides to sell Arab the latest weapon, Ali lost the fight, Four Seas Players, Asian American Dance Company), Sep 1977-Feb 26, 1978; cuid1732 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 102)
  - Video 103: Feb 19, 1978 Broadcast tape Play, cuid1733 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 103)
    Duration: 33:27
  - Video 104: Feb 26, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1734 (Box 82, Half inch video reel Video 104)
    Duration: 28:15
  - Video 105: March 5, 1978 Broadcast tape News, cuid1735 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 105)
    Duration: 28:34
  - Video 106: March 5, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1736 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 106)
  - Video 107: March 12, 1978 Broadcast tape News (Women's Day), cuid1737 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 107)
    Duration: 23:34
  - Video 108: March 12, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1738 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 108)
  - Video 109: March 19, 1978 Broadcast tape News, cuid1739 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 109)
    Duration: 23:07
  - Video 110: March 19, 1978 Broadcast tape Philippine Immigrants by Leonardo Ignacio, cuid1740 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 110)
    Duration: 31:03
  - Video 111: March 26, 1978 Broadcast tape News, cuid1741 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 111)
    Duration: 25:59
  - Video 112: March 26, 1978 Broadcast tape Asian American Film Festival: The Journey (cartoon), Take Me, cuid1742 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 112)
    Duration: 27:14
  - Video 113: April 2, 1978 Broadcast tape News, cuid1743 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 113)
    Duration: 32:46
  - Video 114: April 2, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1744 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 114)
  - Video 115: April 9, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1745 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 115)
    Duration: 25:19
  - Video 116: April 9, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1746 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 116)
    Duration: 24:29
  - Video 117: April 16, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1747 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 117)
    Duration: 28:28
  - Video 118: April 16, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1748 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 118)
  - Video 119: April 23, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1749 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 119)
    Duration: 30:06
  - Video 120: April 23, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1750 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 120)
    Duration: 30:31
  - Video 121: April 30, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1751 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 121)
    Duration: 30:40
  - Video 122: April 30, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1752 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 122)
  - Video 123: May 7, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1753 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 123)
    Duration: 31:57
  - Video 124: May 7, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1754 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 124)
    Duration: 28:18
  - Video 125: May 14, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1755 (Box 84)
  - Video 126: May 21, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1756 (Box 84)
  - Video 127: May 28, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1757 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 127)
    Duration: 25:41
  - Video 128: May 28, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1758 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 128)
    Duration: 33:00
  - Video 129: June 4, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1759 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 129)
  - Video 130: June 4, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1760 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 130)
  - Video 131: June 11, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1761 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 131)
    Duration: 28:54
  - Video 132: June 11, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid1762 (Box 83, Half inch video reel Video 132)
    Duration: 28:25
  - Video 133: June 18, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36306 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 133)
    Duration: 52:22
  - Video 134: June 25, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36307 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 134)
    Duration: 59:01
  - Video 135: July 2, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36305 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 135)
    Duration: 51:33
  - Video 136: July 9, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36308 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 136)
    Duration: 29:11
  - Video 137: July 9, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36309 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 137)
  - Video 138: July 16, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36310 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 138)
    Duration: 29:41
  - Video 139: July 16, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36311 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 139)
    Duration: 29:00
  - Video 140: July 30, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36312 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 140)
    Duration: 55:31
  - Video 141: August 6, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36313 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 141)
    Duration: 52:42
  - Video 142: August 20, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36314 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 142)
    Duration: 33:40
  - Video 143: August 20, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36315 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 143)
    Duration: 25:34
  - Video 144: September 3, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36316 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 144)
    Duration: 31:37
  - Video 145: September 3, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36317 (Box 84, Half inch video reel 145)
  - Video 146: September 17, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36318 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 146)
    Duration: 54:59
  - Video 147: September 24, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36319 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 147)
  - Video 148: October 1, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36320 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 148)
  - Video 149: October 8, 1978 Broadcast tape - Highlights of CCTV 3rd TV Production and Performance Workshop with students' assignment, cuid36321 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 149)
    Duration: 32:03
  - Video 150: October 15, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36322 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 150)
    Duration: 32:45
  - Video 151: October 15, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36323 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 151)
    Duration: 30:56
  - Video 152: October 22, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36324 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 152)
    Duration: 59:04
  - Video 153: October 29, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36325 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 153)
    Duration: 59:34
  - Video 154: November 5, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36326 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 154)
    Duration: 29:27
  - Video 155: November 19, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36327 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 155)
    Duration: 32:49
  - Video 156: November 25, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36328 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 156)
    Duration: 29:31
  - Video 157: December 10, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36329 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 157)
    Duration: 33:03
  - Video 158: December 24, 1978 Broadcast tape, cuid36330 (Box 85, Half inch video reel 158)
    Duration: 1:01:03
  - Video 159: January 7, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36331 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 159)
    Duration: 1:04:04
  - Video 160: January 4, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36332 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 160)
    Duration: 31:13
  - Video 161: January 14, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36333 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 161)
  - Video 162: January 28, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36334 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 162)
    Duration: 1:04:51
  - Video 163: February 11, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36335 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 163)
    Duration: 27:26
  - Video 164: February 11, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36336 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 164)
    Duration: 32:39
  - Video 165: February 18, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36337 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 165)
  - Video 166: February 25, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36338 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 166)
  - Video 167: February 25, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36339 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 167)
  - Video 168: March 4, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36340 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 168)
  - Video 169: March 4, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36341 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 169)
  - Video 170: March 11, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36342 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 170)
  - Video 171: March 18, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36343 (Box 86, Half inch video reel 171)
  - Video 172: March 18, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36344 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 172)
  - Video 173: March 25, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36345 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 173)
  - Video 174: April 1, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36346 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 174)
  - Video 175: April 8, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36347 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 175)
  - Video 176: April 22, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36348 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 176)
  - Video 177: April 29, 1979 Broadcast tape - News, cuid36349 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 177)
  - Video 178: May 6, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36350 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 178)
  - Video 179: May 6, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36351 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 179)
  - Video 180: May 13, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36352 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 180)
  - Video 181: May 13, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36353 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 181)
  - Video 182: May 20, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36354 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 182)
  - Video 183: May 27, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36355 (Box 87, Half inch video reel 183)
  - Video 184: June 3, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36356 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 184)
  - Video 185: June 10, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36357 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 185)
  - Video 186: June 10, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36358 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 186)
  - Video 187: June 17, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36359 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 187)
  - Video 188: June 17, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36360 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 188)
  - Video 189: June 24, 1979, cuid36361 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 189)
  - Video 190: June 24, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36362 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 190)
  - Video 191: July 1, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36363 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 191)
  - Video 192: July 8, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36364 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 192)
  - Video 193: July 15, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36365 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 193)
  - Video 194: July 15, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36366 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 194)
  - Video 195: July 22, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36367 (Box 88, Half inch video reel 195)
  - Video 196: July 29, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36368 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 196)
  - Video 197: July 29, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36369 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 197)
  - Video 198: August 5, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36370 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 198)
  - Video 199: August 5, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36371 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 199)
  - Video 200: August 12, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36372 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 200)
  - Video 201: August 12, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36373 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 201)
  - Video 202: August 19, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36374 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 202)
  - Video 203: August 19, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36375 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 203)
  - Video 204: August 26, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36376 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 204)
  - Video 205: September 2, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36377 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 205)
  - Video 206: September 2, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36378 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 206)
  - Video 207: September 23, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36379 (Box 89, Half inch video reel 207)
  - Video 208: September 30, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36380 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 208)
  - Video 209: October 7, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36381 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 209)
  - Video 210: October 14, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36382 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 210)
  - Video 211: October 14, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36383 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 211)
  - Video 212: October 21, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36384 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 212)
  - Video 213: October 21, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36385 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 213)
  - Video 214: November 4, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36386 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 214)
  - Video 215: November 11, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36387 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 215)
  - Video 216: November 18, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36388 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 216)
  - Video 217: November 25, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36389 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 217)
  - Video 218: December 2, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36390 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 218)
  - Video 219: December 9, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36391 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 219)
  - Video 220: December 16, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36392 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 220)
  - Video 221: December 23, 1979 Broadcast tape, cuid36393 (Box 90, Half inch video reel 221)
  - Video 222: CCTV, January 6, 1980; Cuid9268 (Box 91, Video Cuid9268)
    Scope and Contents
    This episode includes three parts: street interviews, a 35-minute film, and an announcement section. In the street interviews, two hosts interview people about the newspapers they read, their views on international and domestic news, their impressions of last year, and their hopes for the coming year. The second part of the episode is a Curtis Choy film Dupont Guy: The Schiz of Grant Avenue (1976). The film narrates the struggles and experiences of being Chinese American.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 52 minutes
  - Video 223: CCTV, January 13, 1980; Cuid9269 (Box 91, Video Cuid9269)
    This episode includes several parts: street interviews, coverage of a photo exhibition and a variety show, a 9-minute documentary, and an announcement section. In the street interviews, two hosts interview people about their views on subways in the city. The photo exhibition shows two Chinese photographers' works that depict life in Chinatown, including sweatshop laborers and street demonstrations for employment equality. The variety show is called China Nite and is organized by a local middle school. The documentary film contains intertitles that read Brute Force Cybernetics presents Second Campaign and Berkeley May 1969.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration: 53 minutes
  - Video 224: CCTV, January 20, 1980; Cuid9270 (Box 91, Video Cuid9270)
    This episode includes three parts: a news report on a local demonstration, a 19-minute documentary, and an announcement section. The first part covers housing issues faced by a group of Chinatown residents, who organized demonstrations against the landlord Thomas Sung. Interviews with the disaffected tenants and Thomas Sung () are included. The second part shows a documentary film Jenny (1977), which is produced by Japanese American Ginny Hashii. The documentary narrates the experiences of being Japanese American in the United States.
    Format: 3/4" Umatic, Duration 55 minutes.
  - Video 225: CCTV, January 27, 1980; Cuid9271 (Box 91, Video cuid9271)